alrwaq.net 2013-03-15

# Alrwaq trd. - Privacy Statement

**Information we may collect from you**

We may collect and process the following data about you:

Information provided by filling out the forms on our site. This includes information provided at the time of registration, account, and purchase services from us or request more services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site or services purchased;

A record will be kept of any request  and or information received by email or letter from the customer; 

We may also collect some information from surveys that u complete, surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them; 

Details of transactions you carry out through our site are also kept in a record; and details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access and use. 

  We may collect information about your computer, your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. It is important to know that this is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. 

  For the same reason, we may collect information about your general Internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us: 

  To estimate our audience size and usage pattern; 

  To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customize our site according to your individual interests; 

  To speed up your searches; and 

  To recognize you when you return to our site. 

  You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site. 

**Your personal data**

             Passwords and user names are your responsibility to keep them confidential and not to share them with anyone. 

Although the transmission of information via the Internet is not secure %100, we will strive to protect your personal data. However, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. 

**How we use the information?**

The information we have that is provided you is used the following ways: 

To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; 

To provide you with information, offers that may interest and suites the type of computer or internet service you are using. 

  To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us; 

To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so; 

To notify you about changes to our service

  If you have placed an order for our services, we will use the information we hold to send you our regular newsletter. This newsletter is our primary method of communicating with you and will inform you of changes to our site, notify you of planned outages and updates to our services, and keep you informed about our services generally. By placing an order for our services, you consent to us using the information we hold about you in this way. 

  If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you. 

**Disclosure of   information**

We may disclose your personal information to third parties: 

In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets; or 

If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use or terms and conditions of supply and other agreements; or to protect our rights, property, or safety, or that of our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**Disclosure of your information**

         Please note that policies may change from site to another. So if you visit a site linked in our site, please keep in mind that they may have privacy policies differ from ours; and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

**Changes to our privacy policy**

       Customers will be notified about any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future. 

**Contact**

  Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to info@alrwaq.net
